Guide to the Friendship House Association records, 1904-1992 MS2142
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Activities, 1919-1990; MS2142 Series 3; 15 Linear feet (Box 70, Box 71, Box 68, Box 69, Box 55, Box 67, Box 52, Box 53, Box 43, Box 42, Box 54, Box 56, Box 57, Box 58, Box 59, Box 60, Box 51, Box 50, Box 49, Box 48, Box 47, Box 46, Box 45, Box 44, Box 65, Box 66, Box 61, Box 62, Box 63, Box 64)
  - Christmas carollers from Friendship House, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Activities, undated (Box 45)
  - Programs described, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Potomac magazine article on programs, 1960 ca. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Objectives, 1960 ca. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Draft alternative service considered, 1960 ca. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Persons and situations served, 1960 ca. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Baby care class, 1960 ca. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Art class, 1960 ca. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Special events - clown show, 1960 ca. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Knitting class, 1960 ca. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Halloween, 1960 ca. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Capitol Hill Players (drama group), 1960 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Dramatic production, 1960 ca. (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Christmas events, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Art show, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Washington Post article on Friendship House, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Washington Post article on Friendship House, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Capitol Hill Urban Center proposal, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Food donations from the state of Maryland, 1960-1961 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Recreation - Boys 8-10, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Capitol Hill Players - correspondence, notices, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Capitol Hill Urban Center - proposal, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Peace Corps training site offer, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Job Registry, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Storytelling at Friendship house, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Program "What's Cooking", 1962 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Boys' Recreation (6-8) -, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Various activities pictured, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Proposed urban center program, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Capitol Hill Players, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Neighborhood survey, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Housing of Dc demonstrators, visitors, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Musical program, 1962-1964 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Scope of programs for the, 1960 ca. (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Potomac magazine article, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Group work programs, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Neighborhood Service Project, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Capitol Hill Players, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Capitol Hill Urban Center - proposal, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Article on Miss Burklin and Friendship House programs, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Neighborhood survey, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Neighborhood survey, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 41)
  - General group work, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 42)
  - Various activities, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 43)
  - Various benefits, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 44)
  - DC Recreation Facilities - map, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 45)
  - Block Clubs, 1964-1965 (Box 45, Folder 46)
  - Urban Service Corps site, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 47)
  - Activities, undated (Box 46)
  - Summary of programs, 1942-1965 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Article describing programs, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Drama program proposal, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Job Registry, 1965-1967 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Notices, supervisors' notes, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Report to the Executive Director - "What's Going On", 1967 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Testimony summarizing programs, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Art show, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Group work, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Job Placement Program, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Beautification ( Mrs. Johnson's program), 1967 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Playground activities, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Work and Training Opportunity Center, 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Programs, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Article in Spectator, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Job Program - monthly reports, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Report to Director, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Report to Director, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Tutorial Program, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Poor Peoples' Campaign participation, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Group Work, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Reports to Executive Director, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Reports to Executive Director, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Children's room, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Programs, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Reports to Executive Director, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Reports to Executive Director, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Reports to Executive Director, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Reports to Executive Director, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Adult Education - monthly reports, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Fire bombing, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Photo of child, 1969-1970 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Activities, undated (Box 47)
  - Programs and activities outlined, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Programs and activities outlined, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Programs and activities outlined, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Programs and activities outlined, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Programs and activities outlined, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - "A Working Paper: Friendship House DevelopmentProject, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Community service project, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Drama group, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Friendship House van, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Seniors (the Aged) dinner, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Bingo game, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Sewing club, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Christmas party, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Unidentified persons, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Unidentified persons, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified persons, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Photos of some Redskins players, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Dance program, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Dance program, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Dance program, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Football, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Boys on the playground, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Programs, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Children visit a government office, 1970 ca. (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Programs outlined, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Planning project, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Arts Center proposal, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Dance programs in funding request - described, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Drama program - described in funding proposal, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Brochures on programs, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - List of activities at Friendship House, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Bicentennial celebration events, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - The Edmonds School Case - community involvement, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Block parties, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - SHACK Detox Clinic, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Programs outlined, 1973 ca. (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Programs - newspaper article on, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Community Arts Center proposal, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Playground, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - History - highlights of programs, done in 1974, 1904-1973 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Objectives, outlines of programs, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Mary McCloud Bethune statue dedication, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Activities - dance and drum program, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Programs outlined, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - Activities outlined for Budget Request Form, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - Activities, undated (Box 48)
  - Programs - general article on, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Evaluations, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Bicentennial projects, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Draft - of Family Planning Service proposal, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Evaluation services at Friendship House, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Programs outlined in UPO newsletter, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Programs summarized, brochure -, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Programs summarized, brochure -, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Programs summarized, brochure -, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Buzzard's Point Committee, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Market Day, in a newspaper article, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Aims and objectives of program; statistics, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Aims and objectives of program; statistics, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Buzzard's Point Committee, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Capital Gateway Corporation (Buzzard's Point), 1978 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Capital Gateway Corporation (Buzzard's Point), 1978 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Young Mothers' Club, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Dance, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Legal assistance service - application, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Programs outlined, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Programs outlined, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Dances, 1980 ca. (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Art show, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Art show, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous photos, 1980 ca. (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Art show, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Unemployment statement, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Rosalyn Carter's work appreciated, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Unemployment - testimony in a case, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Article on Friendship House programs, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Assessment of all programs, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Activities and the house, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Psycho-Social Rehabilitation Program, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Psycho-Social Rehabilitation Program, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Photo of unidentified woman and dog n.d., undated (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Acupuncture demonstration n.d., undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Activities, undated (Box 49)
  - Day Camp, summer programs - swimming, 1940 ca. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Day Camp, 1941 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Day Camp, 1942 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Day Camp, 1944 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Summer Camp, swimming, 1950 ca. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Day Camp, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Day Camp, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Day Camp, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Day Camp, 1960-1967 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Day Camp, 1960-1967 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Day Camp, 1960-1967 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Day Camp, 1960-1967 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Day Camp - Ellen Wilson Center, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Day Camp, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Day Camp, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Block Camp, 14th and G Streets, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Potomac Gardens Block Camp, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Day Camp - Ellen Wilson Center, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Day Camp - Ellen Wilson Center, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Day Camp, 1970 ca. (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Day Camp proposal, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Activities, undated (Box 50)
  - Camp Friendship: Brochures and program, 1950-1953 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Camp Friendship materials, 1952-1957 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Camp Friendship materials, 1952-1957 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Camp Friendship materials, 1952-1957 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Camp Friendship materials, 1952-1957 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Camp Friendship materials, 1952-1957 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Camp Friendship materials, 1952-1957 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Camp Friendship materials, 1952-1957 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Camp Friendship - payments, registration, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Camp Friendship - budget figures, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Camp Friendship material, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Report on Camp Friendship, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Camp Friendship material, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Camp Friendship material, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Camp Friendship material, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Report and study on Camp Friendship, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Report and study on Camp Friendship, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Camp Friendship: Map of location of camp, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Camp Friendship: Accounts, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Camp Friendship: Accounts, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Camp Friendship, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Camp Friendship, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Camp Friendship, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Camp Friendship, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Camp Friendship: Contribution by Congressional Secretaries Org., 1966 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Camp Friendship: Newspaper photo, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Camp Friendship: Suggested improvements, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Camp Friendship, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Camp Friendship, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Camp Friendship: Mid season report, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Camp Friendship: Discussion of sale of camp, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Camp Friendship: Sale of property, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Camp Friendship: Sale check and mortgage pay off, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Activities, undated (Box 51)
  - Programs described, article, 1936 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - . Photo of day care children, 1940 ca. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Day Home brochures and statistics, 1940-1949 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Day Home brochures and statistics, 1940-1949 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Day Home brochures and statistics, 1940-1949 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Day Home brochures and statistics, 1940-1949 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Day Home brochures and statistics, 1940-1949 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Day Home brochures and statistics, 1940-1949 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Children in day care, 1950 ca. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Children doing art work, 1950 ca. (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Day Care (Day Home), 1950-1951 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Day Care (Day Home), 1950-1951 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Washington Star magazine article, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Day Home enrollment figures, 1952-1955 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Day Home enrollment figures, 1952-1955 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper article, 1953 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Day care, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper photo, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Day care helpers, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Day care, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Staff, correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Staff, correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Day care - statistics, enrollment, 1958-1959 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Day care - statistics, enrollment, 1958-1959 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Day Home study, program, 1959 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Day care "What it is and Does" Report, 1959 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Program and a recreation committee meeting, 1959 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Day Home study committee report, 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Day care - forms, letters to parents, 1960 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Day care - statistics, 1961-1962 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Day care - statistics, 1961-1962 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Program described, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Day care fee scale, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Newspaper article - children's finger games, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Day care - statement, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Day care, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Eye tests, newspaper photos, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Day care, 1965-1966 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Day care, 1965-1966 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - Day care, 1965-1966 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Child Development Center - list of activities, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - Day care statistics, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - Activities, undated (Box 52)
  - Day Care - statistics, narratives, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Day Care - statistics, narratives, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Day Care - statistics, narratives, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Day Care - general and monthly reports, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Day Care - general and monthly reports, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Day Care - general and monthly reports, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Washington Post article, photos on day care, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Day care statistics and monthly reports, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Day care statistics and monthly reports, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Day care statistics and monthly reports, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Day care statistics, monthly reports and rules, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Day care statistics, monthly reports and rules, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Day care statistics, monthly reports and rules, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Day care program outline, monthly reports, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Day care program outline, monthly reports, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Child Development Center, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - CDC - Director's job advertised, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - CDC - Newsletter, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Child's photo at CDC in HEW newsletter, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - CDC - delinquent payment letter samples, 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - CDC -, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Proposal - Rockport Foundation - to update playground, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - CDC, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - CDC, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - CDC, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Testimony regarding CDC -, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - CDC and DC Public Schools - food program agreement, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - CDC - daily planning, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - CDC staff resumes, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - CDC Information Bulletins for parents, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - CDC sample letter to parents, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - CDC delinquent fee letters (samples), 1977 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - CDC - DC Government contract for services, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - CDC research program with Howard University, 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - CDC job announcement, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - CDC questionnaires, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - CDC - HEW compliance form, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - CDC - DC Government Employer Information Report, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - CDC DC Government Contract Renewal Forms, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - CDC accident reports, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - Day Care, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Day Care, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - Day Care request for funds, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - Day Care -, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 44)
    (from annual report)
  - Child Development Newsletters n.d., undated (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - Child Development Newsletters n.d., undated (Box 52, Folder 46)
  - Activities, undated (Box 53)
  - Nursery School, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Cooperative Play School - by laws, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Cooperative Play School - general, 1965-1968 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Cooperative Play School - general, 1965-1968 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Cooperative Play School - general, 1965-1968 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Cooperative Play School - general, 1965-1968 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Nursery School - Pre-school Program - Potomac Gardens, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - National Capital Child Day Care Association: Material, 1965-1968 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - National Capital Child Day Care Association: Material, 1965-1968 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - National Capital Child Day Care Association: Material, 1965-1968 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - National Capital Child Day Care Association: Material, 1965-1968 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Tutoring Program, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Tutoring Program, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - After School Reading Program, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - "Tutoring at Friendship House" report, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Tutoring - publication of manual, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Tutoring program, 1966-1967 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Tutoring program, 1966-1967 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Project OPEN (tutoring club), 1967 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Tutoring program - orientation, workshops, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Tutoring program described, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - List of tutors, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Tutoring program forms, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Tutoring applications, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Activities, undated (Box 54)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Study Files, 1936 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Study Files, 1937 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Study Files, 1938 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Study Files, 1938 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Study Files, 1939 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Study Files, 1940 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Study Files, 1941 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Study Files, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Study Files, 1945 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Study Files, 1947 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Study Files, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Study Files, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Social Work, field work students, 1960-1970 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Field work students, 1960 ca. (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Social work, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Peace Corps workers trained at Friendship House, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Studies - "C" names, 1962-1963 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Narrative re volunteer work, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Interns - Work study (Title 1-C) students, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case studies - "F" names, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - "Self-Social Work" program, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case work (NDP) Reports, statistics, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Social Work and Case Files: A case file, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Internships - college students, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case work reports (for NDP), 1966 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Student intern's work at Friendship House, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Casework statistics, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Casework services proposal, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Concerted Casework Services Proposal, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Summer Service Corps, 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case files "A" names, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case files "B" names, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case files "B" names, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case files "C: names, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case files "C: names, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - Activities, undated (Box 55)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "D" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "D" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "D" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "E" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "F" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "F" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "G" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "G" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "G" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "G" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "G" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "G" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "G" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "J" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "K" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "L" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Social Work and Case Files: Case Files - "L" names, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 17)